Guide to the Pennsylvania Peace Links Records, 1978-2007 AIS.2004.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject and Outreach Records, 1981-2007; 1981-2000; II.
  - New Material Added, 2011
    - Parade Article Responses, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Paradise, Mary J Personal Newsletter File, 1989-1991 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Peace Links Newsletters, 1984-1995 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Pittsburgh Peace Links Newspaper, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Proclamation, "Month of Peace", 1984 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Peace Primer, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Speech Materials, 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Toys +, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Workshops, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Peace Park Garden Agendas and Meeting Minutes, 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Peace Park Garden Annual Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Peace Park Garden- BU Current, 1991-1999 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Peace Park Garden Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Peace Park Garden Design Concepts, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Peace Park Garden- Equitable Gas, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Peace Park Garden Fact Sheets Documents, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Peace Park Garden Fundraising, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Peace Park Garden Harrisburg, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Peace Park Garden Lawrenceville Projects, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Peace Park Garden Newspaper Clippings on Parks, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Peace Park Garden Notes, 1991-1999 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Peace Park Garden and Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Peace Park Garden: Point State Park, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Peace Park Garden Reports, 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Peace Park Garden: South Side Considerations, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Peace Park Garden: World Federalists, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Outreach Evaluation Records, 1983-2003; III.
  These records mostly relate to evaluations of outreach events and activities, such as presentations and lectures, documented in their planning stages by records in Series II. Folders are organized by year or alphabetically by the title of the event, and contain attendance sheets, Peace Links Report Forms, pamphlets and brochures for events, cost descriptions, location information, evaluations and comments, and newspaper clippings. The series also contains organizational notes, receipts, and programs pertaining to Peace Links Annual Dinner events. These dinners, featuring speakers from around the country and around the world, gave opportunities for Peace Links members to meet and socialize. They also served as awards ceremonies and celebrations of progress made. New materials were added June 2011 in the section entitled, "New Material Added, 2011".
  - Board Member Activity Collection, 1983-2000 (Box 7, Folder 39-56)
  - Board Member Activity Collection, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Outreach Activity Records, 1983-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1-21)
  - Peace Links Attendance Forms, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Peace Links Presentations, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Peace Links Presentations and Lectures, 1983-1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Action for Peace, 1988-1995 (Box 8, Folder 25-31)
  - Peace Links Play Reading, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Peace Panels and Coffee Parties, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Annual Dinners- First Annual Dinner, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Annual Dinners- Spring Dinner, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Annual Dinner, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Annual Dinners- Social Hour and Buffet Dinner, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Annual Dinners, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 38-42)
  - Annual Dinners- Pozner and Levinson Reception, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Annual Dinners, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 44-48)
  - Annual Dinners, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Annual Dinners- Aaron Levinson, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Annual Dinners- Jonathon Schell, Guest Speaker, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Annual Dinners, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Annual Dinners- Lachlan Forrow, Guest Speaker, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Annual Dinners, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Annual Dinners- Pitt Student Union, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Annual Dinners- News Articles and Minutes, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annual Dinners- Dinner Programs, 1984-2003 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Y Series Lectures, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - PL/YW Peace Lecture Series, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - PL/YW Peace Lecture Series, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Peace Panels: Erie, PA, June 8, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Peace Panels: Thiel College, July 27, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Y Series and Action for Peace Flyers, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Film Project Names, "Women for America, for the World", 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lists of Organizations for Women for America, For the World, Spring 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Conflict Resolution Workshop at Carlow College, September 28, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Focus on the Philippines Workshop, March 6, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - China Workshop, February 7, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Start & SDI Workshops, October 5, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Workshops, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Public Relations Workshop, March 4, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Voter Registration Workshop, September 18, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Speaker Training Workshops, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Star Wars/SDI Workshop, February 12, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Future Workshop Ideas, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Workshops-Pitt, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Pitt Informal Program Workshops, September, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Pitt Informal Program Workshops- PIP Supplementary Materials, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Pitt Informal Program Workshops, 1984-1988 (Box 9, Folder 35-39)
  - New Material Added, 2011
    - Annual Dinner, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting, May 1, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Peace Links Annual Dinner Programs, 1985-1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Peace Links Annual Dinner Programs, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Pennsylvania Peace Links Annual Dinner Programs, 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Peace Links Guides, 1985-1999; IV.
  This series consists of guides on how to work at local levels for the goals of Peace Links, including the organization of local chapters. These guides were prepared by Peace Links and include packets of materials used in the presentations. New materials were added June 2011 in the section entitled, "New Material Added, 2011".
  - Film Facts: Women for America, for the World, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Action Guide: Becoming Involved in the Governmental Process, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Basic Facts, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Coffee Party Materials, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - What One Person Can Do for Peace, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - High School Organizing Kit, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Elementary School Kit, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Global Awareness, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Vote Peace, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - How to Talk to Children About Nuclear War, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - How to Start a Peace Links Group, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - How to Work with the Media, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Peace Kit, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Peacemaking in the Religious Community, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Peace Panel Packet, Workshops, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Understanding the Soviets Packet, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Community Organizing Kit, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - National Security in the Nuclear Age, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - House Party Organizing Kit, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Speaker Training, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Speaker Training - Display Literature, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Training Guide for Workshop Session: A Developmental Approach to Conflict Resolution, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Women's Forum, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - New Material Added, 2011
    - Becoming Involved in the Government Process, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Celebrate Peace, Elementary School Kit, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Conflict Resolution Kit, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Global Awareness Kit, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - List/Contacts, Ballet, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Peace Begins Kit, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Peace Links Action Guide - Coffee Party/Peace Panel, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Reach for Peace, High School Organizing Kit, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Starting a Peace Links Group Kit, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Talking to Children About Nuclear War, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Understanding the Soviets Kit, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Vote Peace Kit, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - What Can I do?, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - What Peace Links Does, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Concert for Peace, 1983-1984; V.
  The items in this series revolve around the "Concert for Peace," which took place on May 1, 1984 at Heinz Hall, and featured conductor Andre Previn and pianist Andre Watts. "In Concert for Peace" was part of a national concert series that aimed to heighten public awareness and spur active participation against nuclear weapons. The series contains financial statements, newsletters, buttons, programs, a banner, photographic negatives, and news clippings relating to the concert in Pittsburgh. A concert poster, signed by performers, is included among the items in this series. New materials were added June 2011 in the section entitled, "New Material Added, 2011".
  - Art Programs, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Concert for Peace Banner, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Committee, In Concert for Peace, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Committee Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Concert for Peace Advertisements and Memorabilia, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Expenditures, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Funding and Contributors, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Heinz Hall, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - In Concert for Peace Administrative Files, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Mailing Lists, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Musicians Against Nuclear Arms, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Philadelphia Concert, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Previn, Andre, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Concert for Peace Program, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Public Relations, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Solicitation Letter, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Thank You Letters, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Ticket Printouts, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Volunteers, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Watts, Andre, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - New Material Added, 2011
    - Concert for Peace, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Concert for Peace Poster, 1984 (Map-case 9-3)
- Nuclear Weapons, 1978-2004; VI.
  This series contains information relating specifically to the movement for abolition of nuclear weapons. Materials outline the concerns of Peace Links relating to nuclear disarmament and the Pentagon's "Star Wars" Strategic Defense Initiative program, and focus on lobbying efforts in the United Nations and US Senate, as well as informational campaigns regarding alternatives to nuclear weaponry. These efforts focused specifically on the dangers that nuclear weapons pose to children, and Peace Links sought to involve sympathetic women's and Christian groups in the movement against nuclear weapons. Of particular interest is a planning and curriculum guide for dealing with issues of nuclear war in a classroom setting. There is also documentation relating to the taping of a joint venture between Point Park College and Peace Links for a film program on Star Wars. It features informational items concerning events, films and television shows, newsletters from related organizations, lectures, conferences, and anti-nuclear war reading lists. New materials were added June 2011 in the section entitled, "New Material Added, 2011".
  - Abolition 2000, 1982-2001 (Box 10, Folder 44-45)
  - Arms Control- Articles and Letters to the Editor, 1985-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Arms Control- Miscellaneous Materials, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Arms Control- Weekly Reader clippings, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Children, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Christian, 1985-1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Conferences and Workshops Fail Safe, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Conferences and Workshops Pittsburgh Conference - Elimination of WMD, 1992-2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conferences and Workshops PIP, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Defense and the Economy – Conferences of Women for Responsible National Security, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Defense and Economy Miscellaneous Newsletters and Publications, 1978-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lown, Bernard, Dr., 1985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Tacoma Park, MD Nuclear Free Zone, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Disarmament, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Freeze, 1982-1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Testing, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - "Our Move" Posters, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - USA - Nuclear Sites Posters, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Union, 1981-1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Star Wars, 1980-2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Weapons and Waste Management, Nuclear Proliferation, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Weapons and Waste Management, Nuclear Waste, 1991-1997 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Weapons and Waste Management, Weapons, 1983-1989 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Women, Lise Meitner, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Women, Miscellaneous, 1985-2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - New Material Added, 2011
    - Bee Bee Demonstration, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Nuclear Free Zone, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Nuclear War Information, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Pittsburgh/Beijing and Beyond, 1985-2000; VII.
  These records relate to Peace Links' attendance at the United Nation's Fourth World Conference on Women held in Beijing, China from September 4-15, 1995. A concurrent unofficial Nongovernmental Organization (NGO) Forum, held from August 30 to September 8, 1995, paralleled the themes of the UN conference and included workshops, presentations, and plenary sessions by international participants. Members of the Pittsburgh/Beijing and Beyond '95 group participated in both the UN Conference on Women and the NGO Forum. Some of the Peace Links members traveled to the conference on a "Peace Train" that ran from Helsinki, Finland all the way to Beijing. Topics discussed at the conference included development, education, human rights, health and reproductive rights, and world peace. Despite difficulties, the conference was felt to have accomplished some important advances in the topics discussed.
  This series contains papers pertaining to the preparation for and attendance of the conference and forum. Materials in the collection include a small number of United Nation reports, flyers, newspaper clippings, and brochures, relating to topics discussed at international conferences and the status of women and development in various countries. There are no internal business records, correspondence, or financial statements in this series.
  Researchers may also wish to consult To Beijing and Beyond: Pittsburgh and the United Nations Fourth World Conference on Women, edited by Janice Auth.
  - Beijing, 1994-1997; 1.
    - CMAST Speech, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Conference, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 27-28)
    - Ford Foundation, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Pittsburgh, Beijing and Beyond, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, undated (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
    - The United Nations, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - The Fourth World Conference on Women, September 4-15, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 34-39)
  - Conferences, 1985-1995; 1994-1995; 2.
    - Cairo, Egypt: International Conference on Population & Development, September 5-13, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Nairobi, Kenya: World Conference to Review and Appraise the Achievements of the United Nations Decade for Women Equality, Development and Peace, July 15-26, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Turku, Finland: Nordic Forum - Women's Life and Work: Joy and Freedom, August 1-6, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Copenhagen, Denmark: United Nations World Summit on Social Development, March 6-12, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Vienna, Austria: High-Level Regional Preparatory Meeting for the Fourth World Conference on Women, October 17-21, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Conference Topics, undated; 3.
    - Development, undated (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
    - Draft Platform for Action, undated (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Education, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Equality – Human Rights, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Gender Issues, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Health and Reproductive Rights, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Peace, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - United Nations, 1995; 4.
    - Commission on the Elimination of Discrimination Against Women (CEDAW), undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Peace, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Peace - Nuclear Weapons, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Peace - Peace Keeping, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - United Nations Commission on the Status of Women, undated (Box 12, Folder 19-21)
    - United Nations Correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - United Nations Development Fund for Women (UNIFEM), undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - United Nations Economic Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - United Nations Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - State Department, Pre-Conference, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Non-Governmental Organizations, 1995; 5.
    - American Association of University Women, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Application Forms for Beijing 1995 and NGO Forum, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - NGO Forum, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - NGO - General, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Women's Environment & Development Organization (WEDO), undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (WILPF), undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Beijing and General WILPF Information, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Working Group - Beijing WILPF for Peace, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - World Federalist Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Countdown to Beijing, 1995; 6.
    - Countdown to Beijing: Coalition of Minnesota Women and Organizations Preparing for the United Nations Fourth World Conference on Women, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Peace Train, 1994-2000; 7.
    - Peace Train Materials, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 37-39)
    - Beijing, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Peace Train/China Writings, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Pennsylvania Commission for Women, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Pittsburgh, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Accreditation to the United Nations, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh Material, 1990-1997; 8.
    - Pittsburgh, Beijing '95 and Beyond, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 3-15)
    - Pittsburgh City Council, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Commission for Women, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Hannah Wasserman, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Countries, 1991-1995; 9.
    - Australia, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - China Beijing Conference and Forum, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - General: China, 1991-1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Peace and Disarmament, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Tourist Information, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - General, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Germany, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Romania, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Post Conference, 1993-2002; 10.
    - Beijing, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Beijing Plus 5, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Book Correspondence, "To Beijing and Beyond", 2001 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Development, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Division for the Advancement of Women, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Employment, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Hague Appeal for Peace, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Home from Beijing Writings, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Newspaper Clippings - UN 4th WCW, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Pittsburgh Forum Development, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Post-Beijing Reports, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 38-41)
    - Post-UN 4th WCW Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Thursday in Black, 1995-2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - US Reports on Women for the UN Conference, 1985-1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - White House/Interagency on Women, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Soviet Women's Visits, 1985-1994; VIII.
  This series consists of records of visits to Pennsylvania by members of Soviet women's organizations, and events surrounding these visits promoted by Peace Links. Events represented are: the Russian Women's Visit to Pennsylvania, April 6-May 3, 1992; The Russian Ballet Performance as part of the Linking Through the Arts Project, April 14, 1988; The Fifth General Chautauqua Conference on US-Soviet Relations, October 29-November 3, 1989; The Russian Exchange with Lyudmilla Tereshenko, MD, August 1994; and the Russian Women's Exchange, October 19-22, 1985. New materials were added June 2011 in the section entitled, "New Material Added, 2011".
  - Mayor's Proclamation, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - US/USSR Student Exchange, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Studies Series- Women in the Soviet Union, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - The Samantha Smith Foundation, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Center for Soviet-American Dialogue, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Report from Turkistan, April 6, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - US-USSR Projects, December 1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Proposals Sent: CS Westinghouse, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - US/USSR Exchange, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Exchange – PBT - USSR Exchange, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ballet Ideas, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Ballet Benefit, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Ballet Benefit, April 13, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Ballet 1988 Chronological File (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Working – Ballet, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Project '88 MJP Notebook, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - USA/USSR Ballet Exchange, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Dancers Exchange Part II, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Benedum – Pgh. Ballet Theatre Clippings, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - US/USSR Exchange-Donetsk, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Chapter – Fundraising – Outreach, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Contributors, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Fundraising, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Fundraising Letters Samples, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Grant Material File, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
  - Printed Program, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Kindler/Finances/Ticketing, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Tickets – Promotion, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Media, 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Dancers' Press, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Political Skills Training Program for Russian Women, May 3, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Project '88 - Linking Through the Arts, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Dance – Student Programs Project, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Student's Program, April 14, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Outreach, January 12 – February 1, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Outreach – Development Ballet, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Outreach Contacts Project, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Promotion – Ballet Benefit, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 15)